aljazeerasport.net 2017-04-10

# Privacy Policy - beIN SPORTS

Privacy Policy

Effective: August 10, 2016

Welcome to the beINSPORTS.com website (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes how beIN SPORTS, LLC (“beIN SPORTS”, “we”, “us”, and “our”) collects, handles, and uses personal information collected from users or visitors to the Site (and other sites that we control where this Policy is posted) and its services and users of mobile applications that are offered by beIN SPORTS through the Site or through third party app stores (the “Applications”). By using the Site or its services, or by downloading or using the Applications, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy.

When using the Site (and any related Applications and services), we may ask you to provide all or some of the following information: your name, your address, your email address, banking details, your telephone number, and your age (" **Personal Information** "). We may also ask you to provide your thoughts or answer some questions about your favorite events, personalities, and other subjects of interest to sports fans.

In order to purchase any live events viewable on the Site or the Applications, participate in any contest or message feature, download any content, take part in any other interactive feature of the Site or Applications, or receive information from us, such as newsletters or email regarding upcoming events on the Site (and any related Applications or services) you must register and provide accurate information about yourself to the Site, as the services may not work properly without such information.

We may use the Personal Information you provide to us to do some or all of the following:

-          provide you with personalized visits to the Site;

-          recommend goods, services or promotions which may be of interest to you (but only where you have requested us to do so);

-          develop our offers and the layout of our Site or Applications to ensure that our services are as useful and enjoyable as possible;

-          contact you in order to conduct market research; and

-          send out email alerts you may have signed up for.

We will not, however, sell or lease your Personal Information to third parties not associated with beIN SPORTS, its partners, sponsors, and affiliates.

If you do not wish to receive marketing and promotional communications from us or our partners, sponsors, and affiliates, you can choose to opt-out when providing your Personal Information to us. You can also opt-out by updating your user profile on the Site.

Please note: If you do decide to opt-out of receiving information, we will be unable to keep you informed of any new products, services, or special offers that may interest you and will have an impact on our ability to inform you of any live events or important information as part of any subscription service you may have.

**Linked Sites**

The Site may, from time to time, provide links to other third party websites (“Linked Sites”) which are outside our control and not covered by this Policy and may have privacy policies that are different from this Policy. beIN SPORTS is not responsible for the acts or omissions of any Linked Site. You are encouraged to review the privacy policies posted on all Linked Sites before using them or providing them personal information.

**Children**

Our Site and services do not and will not target and are not intended to solicit or attract children. beIN SPORTS does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information. For the purposes of this Policy, children means anyone under the age of 13.

**Use of Suppliers**

In some cases beIN SPORTS uses suppliers to collect, use, analyze, and otherwise process information on its behalf. It is beIN SPORTS' practice to require such suppliers to handle information in a manner consistent with beIN SPORTS policies.

**Who collects and operates data and where exactly will data be hosted?**

This data is collected by [OneSignal](https://onesignal.com/) and hosted securely in the United States.

**To Provide Services to Websites and Apps Using the SDKs**

We share the SDK Information with service providers, contractors and other companies to fulfil your orders, operate our business, communicate with you and make available our Services and this Website.  For instance, we may share certain of the information we collect or receive with companies that help us with billing and payment, marketing, advertising and email marketing, data enhancement (e.g., to provide more relevant offers), website hosting, technology and customer support, web and marketing analytics, anti-fraud or security operations, and other operational, marketing or business support. We likewise may share the SDK Information or Data Segments we create with website operators and app developers (for instance, related to push notifications they send) for their advertising, analytics, or other purposes.

**To Provide Services to Marketers, Advertisers and Platforms They Work With**

We also share SDK Information to provide or help us to provide advertising and marketing services as we have described, including as follows:

With advertisers and their marketing providers, so they may provide targeted content and advertising to you on websites and mobile applications

With other third parties that target advertising.  For those familiar with the online ad ecosystem, these may include demand-side and supply-side advertising platforms, data management platforms, advertising agency trading desks, proximity solution providers, and other advertising technology providers, so they may provide targeted content and advertising to End Users and others on third-party websites, mobile applications, and other advertising mediums (email, direct mail, display media), and so that they may measure the effectiveness of this marketing.

Similarly, we may work with service providers who, to enhance consumer privacy, use a non-human readable “hashed” version of Information such as an email address when sending advertising offers by email or display advertising (which may be linked to a cookie as described above).

Sometimes we provide information (such as IP address, but excluding precise lat/long coordinates) to third party platforms to help advertisers identify common users across different devices or browsers – for instance, to identify a common set of users on both mobile devices and tablets, as well as the web.

**What is the purpose of this collection and processing?**

To Provide Our App and Website Services.  We use the SDK Information to offer and support app and website features provided through the SDKs, including those related to push notifications.  This includes, for instance, providing customer, technical and operational support for these features, detecting and protecting against errors, fraud, or other criminal activity; resolving disputes and enforcing our EULA and other rights we may have.   It also includes analysing, customizing, and improving the features we offer Clients.

To provide information and analytics to our Clients about the use of these app and website features provided through the SDKs, or to help app developers and website operators create or enhance user profiles.

To create inferences about End Users categorized into “Data Segments” or to help Clients do so.  For instance, if SDK Information indicates that a particular device is frequently seen at restaurants, we might categorize a user for targeting of local restaurant offers.  Or, if a user is frequently seen at sports stadiums, we might categorize the user as a “Sports Fan.”

To develop and use “predictive models” – data models that try to predict End Users’ potential future behavior and interests on a per-device basis or across devices

**How long will the collected data be stored (by One Signal, beIN SPORTS and/or beIN Media Group?)**

OneSignal does not have any specific policies in place for limiting the duration that data is stored.

**What are the measures in place to insure security and confidentiality of application user’s information?**

OneSignal have administrative, technical, and physical safeguards in place in our physical facilities and in our computer systems, databases, and communications networks that are designed to protect information contained within our systems from loss, misuse, or alteration.  No method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee absolute security of your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information.

**Consumer Control & Opt-Out Options**

In most cases, consumers have control over whether or not they would like to receive relevant advertisements and marketing email from our Clients.

  **Opting Out of OneSignal Push Notifications**

You may in most cases opt out of receiving push notifications by going to your device “Settings” and clicking on “Notifications,” and then changing those settings for some or all of the apps on your device.  (Different device configurations, or updates to devices, may affect or change how these settings work.)

Your choice to opt out of “Notifications” from the OneSignal platform will not affect ads placed by any other organization.

**Opting Out of Online Interest-Based Advertising**

You can opt out of many of the platforms and service providers that facilitate online interest-based advertising by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s consumer education and opt-out page, at [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).  This type of opt out is cookie-based, which means that if you replace or upgrade your browser, or delete your cookies, you will need to opt out again.  Opting out in this way will not prevent you from receiving ads – it will just make the ads you see less customized to you. 

**Opting Out of “Cross-App” Advertising on Mobile Devices**

You can opt out of having your mobile advertising identifiers used for certain types of interest-based (also called “cross-app”) mobile behavioural advertising, by accessing the “settings” on your Apple or Android mobile device, as follows:

Apple Devices:  If you have an Apple device, you can opt out of most app-based tracking for interest-based advertising by updating to iOS 6.0 or higher and setting Limit Ad Tracking to ‘ON.’ You can do this by clicking on Settings -> General -> About -> Advertising and toggling Limit Ad Tracking to ‘ON.’

Android Devices:  If you have an Android device, you can opt out of most app-based tracking for interest-based advertising by opening the Google Settings app on your device, selecting Ads, and then selecting the option to opt-out of interest-based ads.

Please note that these platforms control how these settings work, so the above may change.  Likewise, if your device uses other platforms not described above, you should check the settings for those devices. "

**Cookies**

We use cookies in order to ensure the website functions properly and to improve your user experience. Cookies are usually a string of numbers and/or letters that a website transfers to your hard drive. The cookies enable the website to “remember” you, either for the duration of your visit (session cookies) or for repeat visits (persistent cookies). We recommend that you visit the websites [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/) if you would like in-depth information about cookies.

On the Site, we use the following types of cookies:

Strictly necessary cookies - These cookies are essential to enable you to navigate around the site securely and to provide you with services you have specifically requested. For instance, they help ensure that payments are processed securely.

Functionality cookies - These cookies enhance the functionality of the website by storing your preferences. For instance, they can remember your name and location, if you provide this information.

Performance cookies -These cookies improve the performance of the website. For instance, they help pages load quicker.
